Finding aid for the R.B. Kitaj papers LSC.1741
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 10. Judaica, 1937 - 2007; 45 boxes
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Color photograph -- Circumcision chair, undated; 1 item. (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Center for Jewish Art: The Hebrew University of Jerusalem -- Newsletter, Summer 1998 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Netafim: Drip Irrigation Systems -- Sales brochure, Undated. (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Exhibition announcement, postcard, thank you card, 1993, 1997, 1999; 3 items. (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletters, March 1995; May 1995; 2 items. (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletter, April 1995 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - Psychology and Kabbalah By Z'Ev Ben Shimon Halevi -- Excerpts, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Call Him Charles by Stephen Fredman -- Essay, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1988 - 1999 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Menard Press, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - "Nationalism, the Jews, and Art History" by Margaret Olin, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - "Another Place" by Nehama Hillman, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - "Kunstgeschichte als vergleichende Kulturwissenschaft: Aby Warburg, die Pueblo-Indianer und das Nachleben der Antike" by Salvatore Settis, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletters, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletters, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1995 - 2000 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - "The Secret of the Gentiles" by David Plante, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - "A La Recherche D'e L'art Ashkénaze" by Seth Wolitz, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletter, October 1993 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Annotated photocopies of various essays, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - "Claude Vigée: an interview" by Anthony Rudolph, October/November 1995 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Natal: The Israel Support Center for Victims of Psychonational Trauma, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - "Her Jewish State" by Roger Cohen, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletter, May-June 1997 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Sidney Delevante -- Resume/CV, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletter, April 1997 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1988 - 2001 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Pie in the Sky -- chronology by Kitaj, undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Is Jordan Palestine? by Daniel Pipes and Adam Garfinkle, October 1988 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Commentary Magazine, October 1990 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Dulwich Picture Gallery -- Programme of Events, May - August 1998 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - UCLA Center for Jewish Studies -- Event announcements, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Derek Boshier: Journey/Israel Project -- Exhibition announcement, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Chagall: Love and the Stage, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletters, 1993 - 1994 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Jerusalem Studio School -- program booklet, 1997 - 1998 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Invitations and exhibit announcements, 1998; 3 items. (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1987 - 1998 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Sukkot/The Booth, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - "Hannah and the Magician" by Richard Wolin, 1995 - 1997 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - The Birth of Shylock and the Death of Zero Mostel by Arnold Wesker -- prospectus, undated (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Book Review: The Birds'-eye View of The Gulf War, 1990 by Anne Atik, undated (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - The Jewish Quarterly, Winter 1967/8 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Brochures, 1983, undated; 2 items. (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - Center for Jewish Art: The Hebrew University of Jerusalem -- Newsletter, Summer 1997 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Harvey Breverman, Nightworks: Metaphor and Memory -- exhibition announcement, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Pakn Treger: The Magazine Of The Yiddish Book Center (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - "In Defense of French Art" by Romy Golan, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - Essays from Common Knowledge at Oxford University Press, Fall 1992 (Box 104, Folder 40)
    - Essay from Yale Companion to Jewish Writing and Thought in German Culture, 1096-1996, edited by Sander Gilman and Jack Zipes, 1997 (Box 105)
    - Lucian Freud -- Tate exhibition ticket, 2002 (Box 105)
    - Der Verlorene -- Print, undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - David -- photocopied essays, undated (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Center for Jewish Art: Publications (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Sight and Sound Magazine, June 1993 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletter, June 1994 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Ohr HaTorah News, February 1998 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Ohr HaTorah: Afternoon Service for Shabbat and Yom Tov -- booklet, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Obituary for Rabbi Albert Friedlander, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Freud is Not Dead by Jerry Adler, 27 March 2006 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Einstein & Faith by Walter Isaacson, 16 April 2007 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, January 1996 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, January 1994 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, January 1984 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Commentary Magazine, June 1990 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings, 1996 - 2000 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1999 - 2007 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - The Price by Arthur Miller -- prospectus, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1982 - 1999 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - The Apocalypse, The Revelation of Saint John the Divine -- prospectus, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1998 - 2000 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1999 - 2000 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings, 1996 - 2000 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings, 1996 - 2000 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Sigmund Abeles: The Max Drawings, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings, 1990 - 1999 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings, 1996 - 1999 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1983 - 1992 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - A Jewish Writer in America -- Saul Bellow, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 1996 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 1989 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1989 - 1991 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1989 - 1990 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Mark Rothko -- Annotated articles (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990 - 1993 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 1997 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 1997 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 1997 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1986 - 1988 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1986 - 1993 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies -- pamphlet and press release, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - "Expressing Exile, 1940 - 2001" -- exhibition announcement (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 2001 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Kaplan's at the Delmonico -- menu, undated (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - First Annual Jewish Cultural Achievement Awards -- program, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Second Annual Jewish Cultural Achievement Awards -- program, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles and clippings, 1992, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, October 1993 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, December 1994 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, February 1987 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, August/September 1987 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - The Jewish Quarterly, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, January 1993 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Commentary Magazine, January 1986 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Commentary Magazine, May 1975 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, June/July 1994 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, April 1991 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, May 1993 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Emily Mason -- exhibition catalog, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 2002 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1992 - 2002 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Illustration with images of various important Jewish men, undated; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - "Memories" -- Unidentified sermon for Yom Kippur, undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - "Autun and Back" by Jed Perl, May 1989 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Announcements and invitations, 2002 - 2003 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1992 - 2002 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Derek Boshier -- exhibition invitation, 2001; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Derek Boshier -- correspondence, 8 September 2001; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Announcements and invitations (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1997 - 2001 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1991 - 1998 (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Tikkun Passover Haggadah Supplement (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 1989 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2001 - 2003 (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2000 - 2003 (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2002 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Prints -- donated, 1980 - 1996 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Undated. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Undated. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Judaica (1 of 3) (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Judaica (2 of 3), 1984 - 1985 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Judaica (3 of 3), 1979 - 2003 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Judaica (1 of 1), 1966 - 2004 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, November 1994 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - The Jewish Quarterly, Spring 2002 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - The Jewish Quarterly, Summer 1994 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Avraham Ofek: The Mural at the University of Haifa, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Archie Rand exhibition catalogues, 2004 - 2005 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Archie Rand The Eighteen: Blessings at the Heart of Jewish Worship, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Archie Rand: The Nineteen Diaspora Paintings, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Bomb Magazine, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Lee Friedlander -- exhibition announcements, 1998 - 2005 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Anslem Kiefer's Book by Max Kozloff, 1992 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Announcements and invitations (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Geoffrey Hartman -- articles, 1988, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Robert Sacks -- article, undated (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Diasporist Manifesto -- excerpt, undated (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - George Segal: Works From the Bible, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous articles (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Fraenkel Gallery, 2001 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (1 of 5), 1984 - 1986 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (2 of 5), 1984 - 1986 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (3 of 5), 1984 - 1986 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (4 of 5) (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (5 of 5), 1983 - 1986 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (1 of 3), 1983 - 1987 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (2 of 3), 1980 - 2001 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (3 of 3), 1974 - 1988 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (1 of 2) (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (2 of 2), 1980 - 1984 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Print -- Unidentified, undated (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Review of David Sylvester, 1992 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - "The Naked Eye" by William Feaver, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - "In the mythical realm of everyday" by Philipp Blom (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Articles and Reviews -- Psychoanalysis (1 of 3), 1990 - 2006 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Articles and Reviews -- Psychoanalysis (2 of 3), 1990 - 2006 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - The Listener and BBC Television Review, November 1960 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - The Sunday Times: The Culture, 4 February 1996 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - "The Morning After" by Benjamin Friedman (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Sigmund Freud (1 of 2), 1980 - 2006 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Sigmund Freud (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Harold Bloom, 1985 - 2007 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Philip Roth, 1997 - 2005 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Philip Roth (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Richard Wollheim, 1974 - 2004 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Heinrich Heine, 1983 - 2007 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - The American Poetry Review, September/October 1997 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Paul Celan, 1984 - 2007 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - Meyer Shapiro (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Isaiah Berlin, 1979, 1997 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Martin Buber, 1961 - 1993 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Rabbi Adin Steinsaltz, 1987 - 1999 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Ludwig Wittgenstein, 1966 - 2007 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Anita Brookner (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Susan Sontag (1 of 2), 2000 - 2007 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Susan Sontag (2 of 2), 1980 - 2007 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Karl Marx, 2000 - 2007 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Theodore Adorno, 1996 - 2006 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Franz Rosenzweig -- Annotated articles (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Clement Greenberg -- Annotated articles, 1980 - 2001 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Rosalind Krauss -- Annotated articles, 1998 - 2004 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Hannah Arendt -- Annotated articles, 1993 - 2007 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Jean Améry -- Annotated articles, 2003 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Gershom Scholem -- Annotated articles (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Balthus -- Annotated articles (2 of 2), 2000 - 2003 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Saul Kripke -- Annotated articles, 2001 - 2005 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Leo Strauss -- Annotated articles, 1997 - 2004 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1999 - 2007 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1984 - 2006 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1983 - 2007 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1991 - 1996 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1991 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1992 - 1998 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1995 - 1997 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1997 - 1998 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1995 - 1997 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990 - 1997 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Holocaust clippings (2 of 2) (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1991 - 1995 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990 - 1994 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990 - 1995 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1986 - 1994 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Hannah Arendt -- Annotated articles (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - George Steiner -- Annotated articles (2 of 2), 1978 - 2004 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - George Steiner -- Annotated articles (3 of 3), 1978 - 2001 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Michael Hamburger -- Annotated articles, 1966 - 2002 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Friedrich Hölderlin -- Annotated articles, 1967, 2006 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Jesus -- Annotated articles (2 of 3) (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Leon Wieseltier -- Annotated articles (3 of 3), 1999 - 2004 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Primo Levi -- Annotated articles (2 of 3), 1999 - 2002 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 - 2007 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Israel and Zionism -- Annotated articles (2 of 2), 2000 - 2001 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Jerusalem Post Magazine (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Jerusalem Post Magazine, 1985 - 1990 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Frank Auerbach, 2000 - 2001 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Lucian Freud: Early Works -- Exhibition reviews, 1997 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - "In the Chair" by Edward Said, 1997 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Isaac B. Singer, 2004 - 2006 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Isaac Babel -- Articles (2 of 2), 2001 - 2006 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 - 2006 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Saul Bellows -- Annotated articles (2 of 3), 2000 - 2002 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Aharon Appelfeld -- Annotated articles (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Marcel Proust (2 of 3), 2000 - 2005 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Sander Gilman -- Articles, 1998 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 1954 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Marc Chagall -- Annotated articles, 1998, 2000 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Philip Guston -- article (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Max Liebermann, undated; 2 items. (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Lucian Frued, 1998 - 2003 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - "Frames of Viewing: Seeing Rothko" -- announcement and poster, 2002 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961 - 2002 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 - 2002 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Frank Auerbach, 1973 - 2002 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Sigmund Freud -- Articles, 2007 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Barnett Newman, 2002 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - The New York Review of Books, 14 May 1998 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Isaiah Berlin -- Annotated articles (2 of 5) (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Isaiah Berlin -- Annotated articles (3 of 5), 1994 - 2002 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Isaiah Berlin -- Annotated articles (4 of 5), 1983 - 2004 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Leo Steinberg -- Annotated articles, 1984 - 2002 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Jed Perl -- Annotated articles, 1991 - 2001 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Asylum in the Library: The Method, Madness, and Magic of Aby Warburg, 2001 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - E.H. Gombrich -- Annotated articles (2 of 2), 1968 - 2002 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976 - 2001 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1992 - 2005 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2004 - 2005 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - New York Times: Book Review (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2004 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2003 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2006 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1974 - 1986 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 5 March 1999 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1988 - 1999 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Skirball Cultural Center -- Nuremberg Laws, 1999 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1995 - 2000 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Life: Special Report -- The Spirit of Israel: 25th Anniversary, 1973 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1974 - 2002 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1977 - 2007 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990 - 2007 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1984 - 1992 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Du: Schweizerische Monatsschrift, October 1951 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, Undated. (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, Undated. (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, Undated. (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - The Jewish Journal of Greater Los Angeles, 24 September 1999 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, Undated. (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, Undated. (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Pound, 1983 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 - 1992 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 - 1990 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 - 1996 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Susan Sontag, 1980 - 1989 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - James Joll, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Aaron Copland, 1990 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 - 1992 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Ludwig Wittgenstein, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Isaiah Berlin, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Father Aleksandr Men (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 - 1990 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 - 1998 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 210, Folder 9)